[{"id": 1769, "question": "Who doesn't love sitting beside a cosy fire on a cold winter's night ? Who doesn't love to watch flames curling up a chimney? Fire is one of man's greatest friends, but also one of his greatest enemies. Many big fires are caused by carelessness. A lighted cigarette thrown out of a car or train window or a broken bottle lying on dry grass can start a fire. Sometimes, though, a fire can start on its own. Wet hay can begin burning by itself. This is how it happens: the hay starts to rot and begins to give off heat which is trapped inside it. Finally, it bursts into flames. That's why farmers cut and store their hay when it's dry. Fires have destroyed whole cities. In the 17th century, a small fire which began in a baker's shop burnt down nearly every building in London. Moscow was set on fire...\n\nQ: The writer considers it    _    to sit beside a fire on a cold winter night .", "options": ["nice", "dangerous", "unhappy", "painful"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 911, "question": "HOGN KONG--Nine out of 10 Singapore citizens returned dropped wallets with money in them,but in Hone Kong only three out of l0 wallets were returned in an honesty test carried out in Asian cities by Readers Digest . Larger cities did worse while in general people in smaller places returned secretly planted wallets,results from the experiment showed. Readers Digest secretly scattered 140 wallets all over Asia,each with a name,address and phone number,family pictures,notes and money in it. The magazine workers then watched to see what happened.South Koreans in Seoul returned six out of the ten dropped wallets,while those in Inchon returned eight. 50 percent of Be dropped wallets were returned in Bombay,Bangkok,Taipei and Kajang in Malaysia,with most people saying they would not keep what was...\n\nQ: The newspaper report is mainly about  _  .", "options": ["how the honesty test was carried out", "where the honesty test was carried out", "the results of the honesty test in Asia", "the results of the honesty tests in the world"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 269, "question": "Should doctors ever lie to benefit their patient---to speed recovery or to cover the coming of death? In medicine as in law, government, and other lines of work, the requirements of honesty often seem dwarfed by greater needs: the need to protect from brutal news or to uphold a promise of secrecy; to advance the public interest. What should doctors say, for example, to a 46-year-old man coming in for a routine physical check up just before going on vacation with his family who, though he feels in perfect health, is found to have a form of cancer that will cause him to die within six months. Is it best to tell him the truth? If he asks, should the doctor reject that he is ill, or minimize the gravity of the illness? Should they at least hide the truth until after the family vacation? Doctor...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["Sometimes government tells lies because they need to meet the public interest.", "Doctors believe if they lie, those seriously-ill patients will recover more quickly.", "Many patients don't want to know the truth, especially about serious illness.", "Truthful information helps patients deal with their illness in some cases."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 59, "question": "A desert is a beautiful land of silence and space. The sun shines, the wind blows, and time and space seem endless. Nothing is soft. The sand and rocks are hard, and many of the plants even have hard needles instead of leaves. The size and location of the world's deserts are always changing. Over millions of years, as climates change and mountains rise, new dry and wet areas develop. But within the last 100 yeas, deserts have been growing at a frightening speed. This is partly because of natural changes, but the greatest makers are humans. Humans can make deserts, but humans can also prevent their growth. Algeria Mauritania is planting a similar wall around Nouakchott, the capital. Iran puts a thin covering of petroleum on sandy areas and plants trees. The oil keeps the water and small tre...\n\nQ: Choose the sentence which best gives the main idea of the passage.", "options": ["The deserts of the world are always changing.", "Man is to take measures to control the growth of the world's deserts.", "Deserts are lands of silence and space.", "Deserts have grown at a fast pace in the past 10 years."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 640, "question": "The Healthy Habits Survey shows that only about one third of American seniors have correct habits.Here are some findings and expert advice. 1.How many times did you brush your teeth yesterday? *Finding:A full 33% of seniors brush their teeth only once a day. *Step:Remove the 300 types of bacteria in your mouth each morning with a batteryoperated toothbrush.Brush gently for 2 minutes,at least twice a day. 2.How many times did you wash your hands or bathe yesterday? *Finding:Seniors,on average,bathe fewer than 3 days a week.And nearly 30%wash their hands only 4 times a day-half of the number doctors recommend. *Step:We touch our faces around 3,000 times a day-often inviting germs to enter our mouth,nose,and eyes.Use toilet paper to avoid touching the door handle.And,most important,wash your ...\n\nQ: Doctors suggest that people should wash their hands   _  .", "options": ["twice a day", "three times a day", "four times a day", "eight times a day"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3090, "question": "How's your relationship with your dad? It can be easy to let walls build up between you during the teen years. But by taking several simple steps, you can help improve the relationship between the two of you--even without great efforts. Here are a few quick tips. Talk it out. Communication is key to any friendship. Open your mouth and let your dad know what's on your mind. Give him a chance to get to know you. Listen up. Your dad's lived more life than you have. Believe it or not, he's probably been there and can help you get through the pressures and struggles. Ask how he dealt with school, girls or temptations . Then pay attention. Take some time. It can be hard for us kids to talk about what really matters. But spending time together can build the relationship, and create chances to tal...\n\nQ: The main purpose of the passage is to advise teenagers on how to   _  .", "options": ["respect and obey their fathers", "communicate with their fathers", "ask their fathers for advice", "get along well with their fathers"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 656, "question": "Many people have influence on my life, based on their personal characteristics, achievements, and values. I have been lucky to have had a great many teachers and professors who I respect for their patience and intelligence. There are artists who have encouraged me by their talents and creativity. I value many political leaders, who have inspired me by their contributions to society, and their ability to change our futures. But of all the people I have known in my life, the person I admire most is my father. As the youngest girl in my family, I always considered myself to be \"Daddy's little girl\". While I grew up, it always made me sad to see so many of my friends and neighbors without a father or father-like figure around. This helped me appreciate how my father always takes an interest in...\n\nQ: What can we infer  about the author?", "options": ["She appreciated her father because he could solve all the problems.", "She considered her father strict and had no smile to her.", "She was outstanding because her father forced her to do so.", "She felt pity for those children without the father."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 387, "question": "A meteor that exploded over Russia's Ural mountains and sent burning to earth has set off a rush to find fragments of the space rock which hunters hope could fetch thousands of dollars a piece. Friday's explosion and following shockwave shattered windows, injured almost 1200 people and caused about $33 million worth of damage, said local authorities. It also started a \"meteorite rush\" around the industrial city of Chelyabinsk,where groups of people have started _ the snow and ice. \"The price is hard to say yet... The fewer meteorites that are discovered, the higher their price is.\" Said Dmitry Kachkalin, a member of the Russian Society of Amateur Meteorite Lovers. Meteorites are parts of a meteor that have fallen to earth. Scientists at the Urals Federal University were the first to announ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true according to the passage?", "options": ["The price of meteorites will be very high without doubt.", "A meteor exploded over Russia's Ural mountains on Friday.", "All meteorites hunters want to sell what they found and become rich.", "People from all across Russia have rushed to Ural mountains to find meteorites."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3351, "question": "Willie Stewart still remembers his first day of kayaking through the grand Canyon. He was getting bounced around in the roughest white water he had ever seen. There was nothing the river threw at him. There he was in a 40-pound boat, with only a few months of training and one arm. Tied to his left shoulder was a prosthetic limb that he'd had for just about a week. The plan was to paddle for 20 days over 227 miles of the roughest white water in the United States. It was one of the most remarkable adventures that the Grand Canyon had ever seen. It started with a casual phone call in the spring of 2005. A good friend, Mike Crenshaw, finally got a permit from the National Park Service to lead a private party of 16 boaters down the Colorado River that coming August. He had a slot open for Willi...\n\nQ: What had urged Willie Stewart to paddle down the Colorado River ?", "options": ["His family's support", "His great determination", "His curiosity", "His dream"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2916, "question": "Most young people enjoy some forms of physical activities. It may be walking, cycling or swimming, or in winter, skating or skiing. It may be a game of some kind, football, hockey, golf, or tennis, it may be mountaineering. Those who have a passion for climbing high and difficult mountains are often looked upon with astonishment. Why are men and women willing to suffer cold and hardship, and to take risks on high mountaineering? This astonishment is caused probably by the difference between mountaineering and other forms of activity to which men give their leisure. Mountaineering is a sport and not a game. There are no manmade rules, as there are for such game as golf and football. There are, of course, rules of a different kind, which would be dangerous to ignore, but it is this freedom f...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the text?", "options": ["Mountain Climbers.", "Mountaineering.", "Mountaineering is gaining popularity.", "Mountaineering is More Dangerous than Other Sports."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 504, "question": "Now some women are spending a weekend at Mother's Camp . There, husbands and children are not allowed. Why would a woman want to take a vacation without her family? Some women say they need time to be alone. At Mother's Camp a woman has room to herself. She can sleep, read or watch TV, and no one will bother her. No children will ask,\"Mom, what's for dinner?\" No husband will say, \"Oh, dear, I can't find any clean socks.\"In fact almost 50% of women in the United States work outside the home. Many of them work full-time and then come home to a second job-taking care of their homes and families. These working women say one of their biggest problems is housework. In the United States, working wives do about 75% of the housework. Many of their husbands say they want to help. But then they burn ...\n\nQ: _    is one of the biggest troubles for working wives in the United States.", "options": ["Housework", "Working outside the home", "When to take a vacation", "Looking after their children"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1000, "question": "Zoe Chambers was a successful PR(Public Relations) consultant and life was going well -- she had a great job, beautiful flat and a busy social life in London. Then one evening in June last year, she received a text message telling her she was out of work. \"The first two weeks were the most difficult to live through.\" she said. \"After everything I'd done for the company, they dismissed me by text! I was so angry and I just didn't feel like looking for another job. I hate everything about the city and my life.\" Then, Zoe received an invitation from an old school friend, Kathy, to come and stay. Kathy and her husband, Huw, had just bought a farm in north-west Wales. Zoe jumped at the chance to spend a weekend away from London, and now, ten months later she is still on the farm. \"The moment I ...\n\nQ: When working as a PR consultant in London, Zoe thought she lived a   _  life.", "options": ["satisfying", "tough", "meaningless", "boring"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3328, "question": "It seems that men are under more stress when stuck in a traffic jam than women. British researchers for the GPS company TomTom used saliva to decide the stress levels. Levels for women were far lower than levels for men. Most of the people taking part in the research, men and women, reported that they didn't feel any stress at all. Even with that report, their saliva told a different story. In fact, people are under stress while in traffic and not even realizing it. That does not mean good things for health. People can only do something about their health if they know something is wrong. Men are more likely to have much less patience than women. That is why their stress levels are much higher than women when they are sitting still in traffic. Men want to get where they are going now. 72% o...\n\nQ: What can we learn about the research?", "options": ["14% of people taking part in it were not affected by traffic jams.", "Researchers used saliva to decide whether people told the truth.", "It was carried out by a GPS company.", "Only British people took part in it."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 397, "question": "The Internet has led to a huge increase in credit-card fraud. Your card information could even be for sale in an illegal web site. Web sites offering cheap goods and services should be regarded with care. On-line shoppers who enter their credit-card information may never receive the goods they thought they bought. The thieves then go shopping with your card number -- or sell the information over the Internet. Computers hackers have broken down security systems, raising questions about the safety of cardholder information. Several months ago, 25, 000 customers of CD Universe, an on-line music retailer , were not lucky. Their names, addresses and credit-card numbers were posted on a Web site after the retailer refused to pay US $157, 828 to get back the information. Credit-card firms are now...\n\nQ: What is the meaning of \"fraud\"?", "options": ["Cheating.", "Sale.", "Payment.", "Safety."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 487, "question": "Lying within, the inner London Borough of Southwark, this hugely improved non-selective Secondary Academy School is looking to recruit and appoint a talented Science Teacher in April 2016 or sooner. POSITION:Science Teacher | KS3 --5| All Science specialists welcome DEPARTMENT:Popular & Ambitious Science Department LOCATION:Borough of Southwark -- Zone 2 -- Inner London PERSON:Qualified Science Teacher required -- experience in UK or overseas trained START DATE:April 2016 or sooner -- full time & permanent contract on offer SALARY:Inner London Pay Scale -- PS29,270 ~PS37,862 a year PERSON REQUIREMENT: All applicants will need to be suitably skilled, trained and qualified to be considered for this Science Teacher position. Applicants should feel confident across Key Stage 3, 4 and 5, in add...\n\nQ: What is a must for the recruited teacher?", "options": ["Being trained in England.", "Experience in UK.", "Diploma of Higher Education.", "Being qualified for all grades."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3371, "question": "Farmer John and Farmer Bob were neighbors. For more than 30 years, they had been getting along very well. Then their good relationship broke. It began with a small thing, then bitter words, and then weeks of silence. One morning Farmer John woke up to find a stream between the two farms. \"It must be Bob,\" John thought. Then one day there was a knock on John's door. He opened it to find a carpenter standing at the doorway. \"I'm looking for a few days' work,\" the carpenter said. \"I do have a job for you,\" John said. \"Look across the stream at that farm. That's my neighbor Bob. He dug a stream between the two farms. I want you to build a fence--an 8-foot fence. I don't want to see his place or his face any more. I don't have such a neighbor!\" The carpenter said, \"I think I know what to do, si...\n\nQ: Just before the carpenter came, John and Bob  _  each other.", "options": ["didn't speak to", "were friendly to", "often fought with", "never had bitter words with"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 108, "question": "Ariau Amazon Towers The Ariau Amazon Towers hotel lets you sleep in a tree house. Eight towers make up this hotel that offers over 300 rooms. If you really want to get into the spirit, book the Tarzan Suite which is large enough for a big family. You'll be thirty feet up in the air and can travel between the towers through their wooden walkways. Prices: starting at $300 one night for each person for a regular room and going all the way up to $3000 for the Tarzan Suite. For more information, visit the website: http://www.ariautowers.com The Ice Hotel Every winter in Jukkasjarvi, Sweden, a special kind of hotel called the Ice Hotel is built. Each year, world-famous artists are invited to design and produce works of art from the ice, many of which can be found in the rooms. You'll have your c...\n\nQ: Which website should you visit if you want to find out whether there exists a hotel under the sea?", "options": ["http://www.icehotel.com", "http://www.ariautowers.com", "http://www.propeller-island.com", "http://www.bahamabeachclub.com"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2348, "question": "Many people keep the stamps in a drawer at home because they'll never know when they might need them! The trouble is that they have no idea of how many stamps they have left. When they want to send something by post, it's very annoying to find out that they have run out of stamps! The Internet is possible to solve the problem. The United States Postal Service has come up with a system which allows people to print their own postage stamps at their own home! This is the perfect solution for those people that have busy lives! Whenever you go to the post office to buy a stamp, you are buying a boring and standard postage stamp. They are red in color, and you can easily buy them on the Internet as well. For example, you can just order a regular 1st class stamp and then print it off using your o...\n\nQ: What's the writer's attitude toward the new type of stamps?", "options": ["He thinks they are a great idea.", "He is afraid they may cause trouble.", "He thinks they save a lot of money.", "He thinks they are as good as the traditional ones."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2705, "question": "Country singer and songwriter Adrienne Young brings together music and agricultural activities.She even included seeds in the album cover of her first CD. Adrienne Young wants people to know that she supports the movement in America to increase local farming.She offers information about agricultural issues on her Web site.And now part of the moneyfrom her third and newest release, \"Room to Grow\",will be donated to help support community gardens. Adrienne Young's family has lived in Florida for seven generations.Her ancestors helped develop the agriculture industry there.The state of Florida is the nation's second largest producer of fruits and vegetables, 'after California. Adrienne Young has said that her interest in nature was shaped by the fact that she did not grow up on a farm.She gre...\n\nQ: Adrienne Young supports to increase local farming in   _   ways.", "options": ["two", "three", "four", "five"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2920, "question": "Hotel Reservations Welcome to the Kampala Beach Hotel Reservations System. You can reserve a room or package one of three ways: (a) online, (b) by phone, and(c)by email. Did you know? You can take advantage of special savings by booking direct with us online. A.Online Reservations Enter your travel dates and the number of guests below to book your room online now. Click here to check on an existing online reservation. If you are searching for a specific package, please make sure your check-in and check-out dates allowing for the minimum number of nights in the package. You may make reservations for a maximum of 4 guests per room. For requests of 10 rooms or more, please refer to Group Accommodations. B.Reservations By Phone If you prefer to reserve by phone, please call: Toll Free from the...\n\nQ: If you want to book a package you have to   _   .            .", "options": ["submit an e-mail reservations request", "make sure of your check-in and check-out dates", "refer to Group Accommodations", "wait for further notice"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3235, "question": "This Monday,the nation will start to celebrate Presidents' Day,just seven days before George Washington's birthday.Everyone agrees that day is a holiday,but is it just to celebrate George Washington's Birthday? What about Abraham Lincoln? Some government offices call it Presidents' Day.Others say the holiday is officially Washington's Birthday.Confused yet? George Washington was elected the country's first President on April 30,1789.Soon after,Americans began publicly celebrating his birthday.Presidential historians say the actual date of George Washington's birth is February 11,1732.But a change in the calendar system 20 years later shifted all dates,making Washington's birthday February 22,which is now well accepted.In 1879.Congress made Washington's birthday an official federal holiday....\n\nQ: What's the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Why people celebrate President Day.", "The history and debate behind Presidents' Day", "To celebrate Presidents' Day or not", "Colorful activities on Presidents' Day"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1772, "question": "Who doesn't love sitting beside a cosy fire on a cold winter's night ? Who doesn't love to watch flames curling up a chimney? Fire is one of man's greatest friends, but also one of his greatest enemies. Many big fires are caused by carelessness. A lighted cigarette thrown out of a car or train window or a broken bottle lying on dry grass can start a fire. Sometimes, though, a fire can start on its own. Wet hay can begin burning by itself. This is how it happens: the hay starts to rot and begins to give off heat which is trapped inside it. Finally, it bursts into flames. That's why farmers cut and store their hay when it's dry. Fires have destroyed whole cities. In the 17th century, a small fire which began in a baker's shop burnt down nearly every building in London. Moscow was set on fire...\n\nQ: How many examples did the writer give to show fires can destroy the whole city ?", "options": ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3451, "question": "It's likely that everything you learned about America's ancient history is wrong. The new book,1491, completely changes our understanding of the America before the arrival of Columbus in 1492. DID YOU KNOW? When Columbus landed there were probably more people in the Americas than there were in Europe. The peoples of North America had such healthy life-styles that as late as the 19th century they continued to be the tallest people on earth. Facts have shown that the Americas were populated as long as 33,000 years ago. 4,000 years ago Mesoamerican farmers developed corn in a feat of genetic engineering that still isn't completely understood. COMMENTS ON 1491 \"In the tradition of Jared Diamond & John MePhee, a totally new view of pre-Columbian America\". -Richard Rhodes \"Attractively written a...\n\nQ: From this passage, we can learn  _  .", "options": ["people settled in the America a little earlier than 1492", "North Americans were the tallest in the 18th century in the world", "Mesoamencan farmers knew genetic engineering 5,000 years ago", "the population in the Americas was smaller than that in Europe in 1492"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1372, "question": "\"Make-A-Wish\" is one of the world's most well-known charities . It makes wishes come true for childrenwho have serious illnesses. It gives them hope and joy and helps them forget about their health problems and have fun. It all started in 1980 in Phoenix, Arizona. Christopher was a 7-year-old boy who was very sick. He always dreamed ofbecoming a police officer. Tommy Austin and Ron Cox, two police officers, made his wish come true. They gaveChristopher a tour of the city in a police helicopter and made a real police uniform for him. There are four kinds of wishes children usually have: I wish to go. Children usually want to travel or go to a concert, a game or a park. I wish to meet. Children sometimes want to meet their favourite actors, singers or players. I wish to be. Some children wis...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["Sick children just wish to get well.", "Christopher and Tommy are two officers.", "A few people are working for \"Make-A-Wish\".", "\"Make-A-Wish\" has a history of over 30 years."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 474, "question": "\"Show them the money!\" That's what some people are saying for college athletes. They say students who play sports for their school should receive salaries. Top athletes should be paid because many of them practice full time, Mark Jameson argues. Rico Cannon, a former college football player, agrees. \"Nonathletes can get a job for extra spending money, but many student athletes spend so many hours in training that they don't have time to work,\" he explains. \"Shouldn't athletes be able to earn extra money too?\" The students also make money for their schools when people buy tickets to their games. The players should receive some of that cash, supporter Robbie Pokora reasons. College athletes are about honor and tradition, but they're also a business. Thanks to ticket sales, there's money for ...\n\nQ: What is Rico Cannon's opinion on paying student athletes?", "options": ["They make money for their schools and should receive salaries.", "Training leaves them no time to work and they should be paid.", "Playing a sport at school is not a job and they shouldn't be paid.", "They can apply for scholarships and should not be paid."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1416, "question": "Water is the most common substance found on the earth, but less than 1% of the earth's water is suitable for drinking. More than 1,000,000,000 people around the world survive on just over 1 galon of water a day. Probebly more than 3,000,000,000 people may suffer from not having enough water by the year 2025. You are considered lucky if you live in a country where you can drink water out of your kitchen tap or bathroom tap. People in some countries have to pay for drinking water at home. So clean water is one of our most valuabe natural resources . In fact, peole waste so much clean water today. In factories lots of water is wasted. At home many people are not taking showers but still baths, and many are brushing their teeth with the tap turned on. Children are no longer taught how to save ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, one of the ways to save water is   _  .", "options": ["to stop keeping gold fish", "to pay much for drinking water", "to use it in a clever way", "to educate those who waste water"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1080, "question": "It's 5pm on a Friday and I'm standing in a coffee shop above Shibuya crossing - one of the most busiest place in Japan where more than a thousand of Tokyo's smartly dressed people gather at eight points, ready to cross - then rush straight for each other. It looks like they must bump into each other, but It's amazing that they all manage to reach the other side safely. But the real reason I'm here is that I want to see people crash. I want businessmen to knock into each other, their umbrellas flying off their arms, and uniformed schoolchildren hitting grannies. Why may I see this now, but wouldn't have had the chance even a year ago? It's very simple - smartphones. Smartphone use is booming in Japan. In 2012, only about a quarter of Japanese used them, most being perfectly happy with their...\n\nQ: Why does the author stand in a coffee shop above Shibuya crossing?", "options": ["Because he is waiting for somebody.", "Because he can have a good view from there.", "Because he wants to see what would happen because of smartphones.", "Because it's interesting to see businessmen's umbrellas flying off their arms"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1111, "question": "Joke l: A man was sitting reading his papers when his wife hit him round the head with a frying pan. \"What was that for?\" the man asked. The wife replied, \"That was for the piece of paper with the name Jenny on it I found in your pocket.\" The man then said, \"When l was at the races last week Jenny was the name of the horse I bet on.\" The wife apologized and went on with the housework. Three days later the man was watching TV when his wife hit him on the head with an even bigger frying pan, knocking him unconscious. Upon regaining consciousness the man asked why she had hit again. Wife replied, \"Your horse phoned.\" Joke 2: \"Do you believe in life after death?\" the boss asked one of his employees. \"Yes, sir, \" the new employee replied. \"Well, then, that makes everything just fine, \" the boss...\n\nQ: What can we learn about the little boy from Joke 3?", "options": ["His father likes to make fun of his mother-in-law.", "He likes to play tricks on others.", "His mother is strict with him.", "His father doesn't like his mother-in-law to come."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1075, "question": "Dutch treat is a late-nineteenth-century term, and it originally refers to a dinner where everyone is expected to pay for his own share of the food and drink. If people go \"Dutch treat\", or simply \"go Dutch\", it means that they will share the expenses of a social engagement. There are many other \"Dutch\" expressions in English, many of which were invented in Britain in the seventeenth century, when the Dutch and the English were commercial and military rivals. The British used \"Dutch\" to refer to something bad, cheap and shameful. A \"Dutch bargain\" at that time was an uneven, one-sided deal; \"Dutch reckoning\" was an unitemized account; and \"Dutch widow\" was slang for prostitute. Later centuries brought in \"Dutch courage\", for bravery caused by drink; \"Dutch concert\", for noisy music; \"Dutch...\n\nQ: According to the passage, some native American \"Dutch\" expressions were related to the German instead of the Dutch, simply because   _  .", "options": ["People hated the German as much as the Dutch.", "People made a mistake at the beginning.", "People made a joke about the German.", "The German immigrants proclaimed that they were Dutch."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 107, "question": "Ariau Amazon Towers The Ariau Amazon Towers hotel lets you sleep in a tree house. Eight towers make up this hotel that offers over 300 rooms. If you really want to get into the spirit, book the Tarzan Suite which is large enough for a big family. You'll be thirty feet up in the air and can travel between the towers through their wooden walkways. Prices: starting at $300 one night for each person for a regular room and going all the way up to $3000 for the Tarzan Suite. For more information, visit the website: http://www.ariautowers.com The Ice Hotel Every winter in Jukkasjarvi, Sweden, a special kind of hotel called the Ice Hotel is built. Each year, world-famous artists are invited to design and produce works of art from the ice, many of which can be found in the rooms. You'll have your c...\n\nQ: For two persons spending a night in one of these hotels, they have to pay at least   _  .", "options": ["$111", "$182", "$600", "$636"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 697, "question": "An old man went to live with his son, daughter-in-law, and a four-year-old grandson. The family ate together at the dinner table. But the elderly grandfather's shaky hands and failing sight made eating rather difficult. Peas rolled onto the floor. When he took the glass, often milk spilled on the tablecloth. The son and daughter-in-law became unhappy with _ . So the husband and wife set a small table in the corner. There, grandfather ate alone while the rest of the family enjoyed dinner at the dinner table. Since grandfather had broken a dish or two, his food was served in a wooden bowl. Sometimes when the family glanced in grandfather's direction, he had a tear in his eyes as he ate alone. Still, the couple blamed him sharply when he dropped a fork or spilled food. The four-year-old son w...\n\nQ: Why were there tears in the old man's eyes?", "options": ["Because he was made to eat alone.", "Because his grandson didn't play with him.", "Because he wasn't given enough food to eat.", "Because his son didn't allow him to live with them."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 48, "question": "A new law helps people with disabilities. The law says that people with disabilities must be able to get into and out of all public buildings. It also says that business must offer special services to people who have special needs. Companies can not refuse to hire disabled workers. Many businesses may have to change their buildings and services. --Ramps must be built so people can get into buildings. --Movie theatres must have space for people in wheelchairs and seats for their friends to sit near them. --Elevators must have floor number in _ . This law will help millions of people. One woman who has been in a wheelchair for many years said, \"It is like a dream.\"...\n\nQ: What do you think the disabled would feel about the new law?", "options": ["They may think the new law reasonable.", "Some of them are sure to be for the new law.", "They must feel very excited and happy.", "They feel it is like a dream."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 488, "question": "Lying within, the inner London Borough of Southwark, this hugely improved non-selective Secondary Academy School is looking to recruit and appoint a talented Science Teacher in April 2016 or sooner. POSITION:Science Teacher | KS3 --5| All Science specialists welcome DEPARTMENT:Popular & Ambitious Science Department LOCATION:Borough of Southwark -- Zone 2 -- Inner London PERSON:Qualified Science Teacher required -- experience in UK or overseas trained START DATE:April 2016 or sooner -- full time & permanent contract on offer SALARY:Inner London Pay Scale -- PS29,270 ~PS37,862 a year PERSON REQUIREMENT: All applicants will need to be suitably skilled, trained and qualified to be considered for this Science Teacher position. Applicants should feel confident across Key Stage 3, 4 and 5, in add...\n\nQ: What should the applicant be able to do ?", "options": ["Teach KS3-5 pupils well.", "Be very confident across Key Stage 3 and 4.", "Be good at using traditional methods.", "Put advanced ideas into practice every day."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3323, "question": "Phyllis Lee of prefix = st1 /Singaporeknew something wasn't right. Her younger son, Alex, then six years old, was getting good grades in his private kindergarten classes. But Lee realized something was wrong when Alex came home one day, crying, with \"zeroes\" on his Chinese spelling test. Lee decided to investigate. According to Lee, the teacher would frequently describe Alex's Chinese writing as 'ghost writings' and made him a laughing stock in class instead of helping him out. Lee, 46, spent the next 12 months teaching Alex and still helps him when necessary. She not only taught him the formation of the Chinese words but also their origin so that he could understand better, often taking more than an hour to read a simple paragraph. Visits to the library and surfing the Internet kept her u...\n\nQ: Alex succeeded in learning Chinese with_.", "options": ["his teacher's guide", "his classmates' help", "his father's influence", "his mother's instruction"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2872, "question": "Both are so much related to each other. And both are so dissimilar! What are the differences between friendship and love? Is platonic friendship possible between persons of opposite sex? Let us try and understand. What is friendship? Why do we call a person our friend? When do we call someone a very good friend? If we care for a person, if we are always ready to help that person and if we share most of our thoughts with a person, they are our good friends. We can always count upon our good friends in an emergency. We are always sure that our friend will understand why we acted in a certain way. We need not explain anything to our very good friends. The friendship is so deep and the relationship is so close, that most of the things are automatically understood by our friends. What about lov...\n\nQ: How do you do to make real friends?", "options": ["You should give others your everything.", "You should share, help and understand each other.", "You should have the same interests in everything.", "Friend in need is a friend indeed."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3143, "question": "My heroes are the Singapore Women's Everest Team.In 2009,they became the first all-women team to climb Mount Everest.The team of six young women trained for seven years before they climbed the mountain.It was difficult for them to train because Singapore doesn't have any snow or any mountains.But they didn't stop,and in the end they made it.They Worked hard every day for their dream so I really admire them. ----Lance Reed, 16, from Britain My mum,Mary Evans,is a real hero.I have a very big family, with two brothers and three sisters.My mum works very hard every day to look after us, and she is very busy.She always makes time for everyone and she always listens to me if I have a problem.I really respect my mum because she always looks after my family and makes sure we have everything we nee...\n\nQ: What do we know about the Singapore Women's Everest Team?", "options": ["They thought of giving up during training.", "They trained very hard outside Singapore.", "They made history as mountaineers.", "They never expected to make it."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2158, "question": "Borrowing to start a business is not easy. Getting a bank loan, particularly for a new small business, is _ Banks favor established-business people with a solid credit rating and a large bank account. They should also have experience in the business they propose to enter, and offer well-prepared business plans that show the ability to repay the loans. If you are not such a person, then you need to double your preparations to convince the banker to lend you that much needed start-up capital . If your business is new and small, bankers will need to know as much as possible about you and your business. However, many small business owners often make the mistake of not being well prepared when going to the bank to apply for the loan. Surprisingly, many loan applicants don't even have the slight...\n\nQ: Banks prefer to give a loan to those who   _  .", "options": ["are in need of start-up capital", "have the ability to pay it back", "own an old and large business", "haven't borrowed money before"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2239, "question": "Once upon a time two brothers who lived on neighbouring farms fell into conflict. It was the first serious one in 40 years of farming side by side, sharing machinery, and trading labor and goods as needed . Then the long cooperoration fell apart. It began with a small misunderstanding and it grew into a major difference, and finally it exploded into an exchange of bitter words followed by weeks of silence. One morning there was a knock on John's door. He opened it to find a man with a carpenter's toolbox. \"I'm looking for a few days' work\" he said. \"Perhaps you would have a few small jobs here and there I could help with. Could I help you?\" \"Yes,\" said the older brother. \"I do have a job for you. Look across the creek at that farm. That's my neighbor, in fact, it's my younger brother. Last...\n\nQ: The best title for this passage is   _  .", "options": ["A Fine Piece of Work", "A Clever Carpenter", "A Conflict between Two Brothers", "Two Brothers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 221, "question": "Bob was born in Cambridge. When he was in elementary school, he asked his mother to take him to parks in their community so he could collect empty soda cans to recycle. His mother agreed, as long as he saved part of the money he earned for college. Bob's mother remembers Bob as the most determined of her seven kids. Bob's persistence paid off. On Friday, he will become the first person in his family, originally from El Salvador, to graduate from college. And he's graduating with university honors. For his honors thesis he researched unmanned solar-powered airplanes, which BYU students have been building and testing for about 10 years. Bob's study helps discover the best way to fly a solar-powered airplane so that it uses the least amount of power. The goal is to design and build an airplan...\n\nQ: From the passage we can know that Bob's honors thesis   _  .", "options": ["makes his mother feel surprised", "helps to save the power of flying a solar-powered airplane", "is done with BYU students", "doubts the way of flying a solar-powered airplane"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2066, "question": "With more and more wineries offering organic varieties to lower their eco-footprint , it's no surprise that they're looking at the environmental impacts of their packaging as well. The making of conventional glass bottles and the corks uses large quantities of natural resources and causes a lot of pollution. Beyond manufacturing, the transport of wine in glass bottles across the country and around the world also has its environmental effect. Trucking all the heavy glass bottles causes a much larger carbon footprint than the transportation of much lighter boxed wine. Almost half the weight of an ordinary case of wine comes from the bottles; about 95 percent of the weight of a case of boxed wine is the wine itself. \"A standard wine bottle holds 750 milliliters of wine and causes about 5.2 po...\n\nQ: The author writes this passage to   _  .", "options": ["call on people to drink less wine", "advise packaging wine with different materials", "advocate using boxes to store wine k@s5u", "introduce how to keep wine fresh after the bottle is opened"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2106, "question": "Ann was on her first package trip in Rosas, Spain. At the hotel, she checked in, and then went to her room to change before dinner. She was just ready to go downstairs when she found that her Spanish money wasn't in her handbag. She carefully looked in all her luggage, but she couldn't find it. All she had was a small purse with ten English pound notes in it! Ann found a place to change her English money. She had very few pesetas , and she would be here for two weeks. On her way back to the hotel, Ann bought some cheese, some bread and some oranges. When she got back, she told the manager that her doctor had told her not to eat Spanish food; she'd just have breakfast each day. That was all right, as she knew the price of hotels included breakfast. For the rest of her holiday, Ann swam in t...\n\nQ: \"A package trip\" probably means   _  .", "options": ["a free trip", "a pleasant trip", "a trip that includes the cost of all the tickets and services", "a long journey"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1311, "question": "History is full of cases where dreams have been a pathway to creativity and discovery. A striking example is provided by Dr. Otto Loewi, a pharmacologist and winner of a Nobel Prize. Loewi had spent years studying the chemical transmission of nerve impulses . A major breakthrough in his research came when he dreamed of an experiment three nights in a row. On the first two nights he woke up and wrote down the experiment quickly and untidily on paper. But the next morning, he couldn't tell what the notes meant. On the third night, he got up after having the dream. This time, instead of making notes he went straight to his laboratory and performed the important experiment. Loewi later said that if the experiment had occurred to him while awake he would not have given it another thought. Loewi...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the author seems to be in favor of   _  .", "options": ["seeking creative solutions", "avoiding scientific experiments", "setting himself after sleeping", "going straight to experiment after the dream"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 690, "question": "Woody Guthrie left California for New York in 1940. There he met Alan Lomax, an expert on America's traditional music. He collected and recorded traditional American folk music, which had few fans at that time. When he heard Woody sing, Lomax knew he had found a true singer of American folk music. Lomax recorded many of Woody's songs for the Library of Congress. Three years later, Woody published a book called Bound for Glory. It was about his early life and travels. From this book people came to learn how Woody had spent his unhappy youth. His mother, Nora Guthrie, died of Huntington's Disease in 1929 when he was only seventeen years old. There was no treatment for the disease. About twenty years later, the disease also began to attack the son. Woody's health got worse and worse, and fina...\n\nQ: From the passage we can learn that Woody   _  .", "options": ["set an example to American folk singers", "became popular when he was very young", "learned a lot from young folk singers", "sang and wrote for all kinds of people"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2493, "question": "Sir, The majority(=Most) of your readers must have been surprised and shocked to read a letter from Mr.R.Hogg,published in last Wednesday's Herald.Mr.Hogg seems to think that his own convenience and that of motorists in general are the only things that matter in our city. I would have supported Mr.Hogg if he had just made suggestions to improve the situation.No doubt his problems would be partly solved if the local government built a multi-storey car park in the city center,instead of encouraging motorists to use public transport.All the same,judging from the tone of Mr.Hogg's letter,I suspect that motorists who are so careless of pedestrians' safety that they would rather park their ears on the pavement than hold up the traffic would probably be too lazy to use a multi-storey car park if ...\n\nQ: The letter above is written in answer to the letter by  _  .", "options": ["art editor", "a certain Mr.R.Hogg", "some readers", "some motorists"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 185, "question": "There are a number of different ways to study a language, each of which has advantages and disadvantages. You may find a combination of these is a best choice for you. If you can find a course in the language you want to learn in your country, this is quite a good way to study. A variety of courses are usually available, including part-time and full-time courses. If you look around, you can probably find a course that suits your needs. The main advantage of such courses is that you'll have a teacher to provide you with instructions, support and with whom to practice your language. You will also be studying with others who are at more or less the same level and you can exchange ideas with them and help one another. One choice is to study a language in a country where it's spoken. There are ...\n\nQ: Compared with two other ways, the obvious disadvantage of studying abroad lies in its    _   .", "options": ["various courses", "high cost", "studying time", "job chances"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 410, "question": "I was brought up in the British, _ . Strong feelings aren't something you display in public. So, you can imagine that I was unprepared for the outpouring of public grief at a Chinese funeral. My editorial team leader died recently after a short illness. He was 31. The news was so unexpected that it left us all shocked and upset. A female colleague burst into tears and cried piteously at her desk. Somehow we got through the day's work. The next day was the funeral. Our big boss stepped forward to deliver a eulogy and was soon in tears. She carried on, in Chinese of course, but at the end said in English: \"There will be no more deadlines for you in heaven.\" Next came a long-term colleague who also dissolved in tears but carried on with her speech despite being almost overcome by emotion. The...\n\nQ: This passage talks mainly about  _  .", "options": ["an editor's death", "bad funeral customs", "western ways of grief", "cultural differences"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2918, "question": "Hotel Reservations Welcome to the Kampala Beach Hotel Reservations System. You can reserve a room or package one of three ways: (a) online, (b) by phone, and(c)by email. Did you know? You can take advantage of special savings by booking direct with us online. A.Online Reservations Enter your travel dates and the number of guests below to book your room online now. Click here to check on an existing online reservation. If you are searching for a specific package, please make sure your check-in and check-out dates allowing for the minimum number of nights in the package. You may make reservations for a maximum of 4 guests per room. For requests of 10 rooms or more, please refer to Group Accommodations. B.Reservations By Phone If you prefer to reserve by phone, please call: Toll Free from the...\n\nQ: If you want an immediate booking, you'd better use\"_\".", "options": ["Online Reservations", "Reservations By Phone", "Reservations By E-mail", "Did you know?"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 456, "question": "A thief who dropped a winning lottery ticket at the scene of his crime has been given a lesson in honesty. His victim, who picked up the ticket, then claimed the PS25000 prize, managed to trace him, and handed over the cash. The robbery happened when maths professor Vinicio Sabbatucci,58, was changing a tyre on an Italian motorway. Another motorist, who stopped \"to help\", stole a suitcase from his car and drove off. The professor found the dropped ticket and put it in his pocket before driving home to Ascoli in eastern Italy. Next day, he saw the lottery results on TV and, taking out the ticket, realized it was a winner. He claimed the 60 million lire prize. Then he began a battle with his conscience. Finally, he decided he could not keep the money despite having been robbed. He advertised...\n\nQ: Hundreds of people phoned professor Sabbatucci because they   _  .", "options": ["wanted to make fun of him", "knew who the robber was", "hoped to get the money", "lost the lottery ticket"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 204, "question": "Reading can be a social activity. Think of the people who belong to book groups. They choose books to read and then meet m discuss them. Now, the website BookCrossing.com rums the page on the traditional idea of a book group. Members go on the site and register books they own that they would like.sham. BookCrossing provides an identifying numb\" .stick inside the book. Then the person 'releases' the book by leaving it in a public place. The hope is that the book will have an adventure, traveling far and wide with each new reader who finds it. Bruce Pederson is the chief executive of BookCrossing. He and his wife Hearer started the site with Ron Hombaker in 2001. Mr. Pederson says, \"One of the founding principles was the two things that change your life: tha people you meet and the books you...\n\nQ: Which of the followings is the east probable place where a member leaves a book?", "options": ["A bookshelf.", "A Mend's home", "A bas.", "A school bag."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 272, "question": "Coral reefs are not just beautiful to look at,but also very useful.They shelter nearly 25% of ocean life and provide food for billions of people.However, like many other species,this amazing ecosystem is in danger of dying out! There are two main reasons for the destruction--the rising carbon dioxide levels caused by global warming as well as human influences like bottom operation.While not much can be done about the former,the loss caused by the latter can be reduced. Bottom operation involves dropping nets to the ocean bed and then dragging them up when filled with fish.This action damaged the ocean floor,causing the coral branches to separate from the reefs.While that is very discouraging,the good news is that if these branches are found quickly,they can be saved.At present,that work is...\n\nQ: Compared with volunteer divers,coralbots   _  .", "options": ["can stay longer underwater", "must work as bees do", "can distinguish what is coral", "can never be damaged"], "answer": 0}]